Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 10: Boxes 572-635
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 10: Boxes 572-635
Kheel Center for Labor- Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 10: Boxes 572-635
6046
Kheel Center
388.2 linear ft.
Pamphlets, publications.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
The Archives Union File is a collection of publications of United States labor unions. Included is information on the American Institute for Free Labor Development. The AUF collection consists largely of pamphlets and publications of unions, collected by the Kheel Center.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Due to the volume of material in this collection the finding aid has been divided into twelve sections.
Section 1: Boxes 1-63
Section 2: Boxes 64-126
Section 3: Boxes 127-191
Section 4: Boxes 192-256
Section 5: Boxes 257-319
Section 6: Boxes 319.1-378
Section 7: Boxes 379-442
Section 8: Boxes 443-506
Section 9: Boxes 507-571
Section 10: Boxes 572-635
Section 11: Boxes 636-699
Section 12: Boxes 700-704
Boxes 650-659 and 661-662 have not been inventoried at this time.
SUBJECTS
Names:
AFL-CIO --Archives; AFL-CIO. American Institute for Free Labor Development--Archives; AFL-CIO. Building and Construction Trades Dept.--Archives; AFL-CIO. Department of Economic Research--Archives; AFL-CIO. Education Department--Archives; AFL-CIO. Executive Council--Archives; AFL-CIO. Human Resources Development Institute--Archives; AFL-CIO. Industrial Union Department--Archives; AFL-CIO. Legislative Department--Archives; AFL-CIO. Public Employees Department--Archives; AFSCME --Archives; Air Line Pilots Association --Archives; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union --Archives; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union. Research Department--Archives; Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America --Archives; American Association of University Professors --Archives; American Federation of Government Employees --Archives; American Federation of Labor --Archives; American Federation of Musicians --Archives; American Federation of Teachers --Archives; American Federation of Television and Radio Artists --Archives; American Guild of Musical Artists --Archives; American Postal Workers Union --Archives; Association of Flight Attendants (U.S.) --Archives; Bakery, Confectionary and Tobacco Workers International Union --Archives; Coalition of Labor Union Women (U.S.) --Archives; Communication Workers Union --Archives; Communications Workers of America --Archives; Congress of Industrial Organizations --Archives; Federation of Westinghouse Independent Salaried Unions --Archives; Hotel & Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union --Archives; Illinois State AFL-CIO --Archives; Industrial Workers of the World --Archives; International Association of Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers --Archives; International Association of Fire Fighters --Archives; International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers --Archives; International Brotherhood of Painters and Allied Trades --Archives; International Brotherhood of Teamsters --Archives; International Ladies' Garment Workers Union --Archives; International Ladies' Garment Workers Union. Educational Department--Archives; International Longshoremens and Warehousemens Union --Archives; International Typographical Union --Archives; International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers --Archives; International Union of North American Laborers --Archives; International Union, Allied Industrial Workers of America --Archives; International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America --Archives; International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America --Archives; International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America. Ford Dept. --Archives; International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers --Archives; Jewish Labor Committee (U.S.) --Archives; National Association of Postal Supervisors --Archives; National Maritime Union of America --Archives; National Writers Union (U.S.) --Archives; New York State AFL-CIO --Archives; New York State United Teachers --Archives; Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union --Archives; Screen Actors Guild --Archives; Service Employees International Union --Archives; Sheet Metal Workers International Union --Archives; Teamsters for a Democratic Union --Archives; Textile Workers Union of America --Archives; United Association of Journeymen and Apprentices of the Plumbing and Pipe Fitting Industry --Archives; United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America --Archives; United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers --Archives; United Glass & Ceramic Workers of North America --Archives; United Mine Workers of America --Archives; United Office and Professionals Workers of America --Archives; United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America --Archives; United Steelworkers of America --Archives; Utility Workers Union of America --Archives; Writer's Guild of America --Archives
Subjects:
Agricultural laborers--Labor unions; Airlines--Employees--Labor unions; Textile workers--Labor unions; Barbers--Labor unions; Building-service employees--Labor unions; Clothing workers--Labor unions; Construction workers--Labor unions; Automobile industry workers--Labor unions; Bakery employees--Labor unions; Transport workers--Labor unions; Fire fighters--Labor unions; Electricians--Labor unions; Plumbers--Labor unions; Teachers--Labor unions; Glassworkers--Labor unions; Restaurants--Employees--Labor unions; Postal service--Employees--Labor unions; Rubber industry and trade--Labor unions
Form and Genre Terms:
Pamphlets.; Publications
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
RELATED MATERIALS
Other sections of this collection:
6046: Archives Union File (AUF)
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 1: Boxes 1-63
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 2: Boxes 64-126
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 3: Boxes 127-191
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 4: Boxes 192-246
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 5: Boxes 257-319
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 6: Boxes 319.1-378
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 7: Boxes 379-442
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 8: Boxes 443-506
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 9: Boxes 507-571
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 11: Boxes 636-699
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 12: Boxes 700-704
Boxes 650-659 and 661-662 have not been inventoried at this point.
Related Collections:
6046 mf: Archives Union File on Microfilm
CONTAINER LIST
- Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers (Box 572, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Constitution - Jan. 1989, Publication (Box 572, Folder 1)
    Author: Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers
    Format: Publication
    Language: English.
  - Item 2: Labor agreement: Effective June 1, 1976, between Scott Paper Company, Everett, Washington and the Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers and its affiliated Locals 183-644, Publication (Box 572, Folder 1)
    Author: Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers; Scott Paper Company
  - Item 3: Labor agreement by and between Crown Zellerbach Corporation, Camas, Washington and the Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers, acting through Local 5: June 1, 1976 - June 1, 1978, Publication (Box 572, Folder 1)
    Author: Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers; Crown Zellerbach Corporation
  - Item 4: Labor agreement effective March 15, 1976, Boise Cascade Corporation, St. Helens, Oregon and the Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers, Local number 1, Publication (Box 572, Folder 1)
    Author: Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers; Boise Cascade Corporation
  - Item 5: Labor agreement effective June 1, 1976, Western Kraft Paper Group, Willamette Industries, Inc. and the Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers, Publication (Box 572, Folder 1)
    Author: Willamette Industries (Firm); Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers
  - Item 6: Labor agreement, May 1, 1976 thru April 30, 1978, Georgia-Pacific, Toledo Paper Division and the Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers and Toledo Local 13, Publication (Box 572, Folder 1)
    Author: Georgia-Pacific Corporation; Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers
- American Radio Association, Publication (Box 572, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: National agreement between American Radio Association, AFL-CIO and various Companies, Agents and Associations, Pacific Coast representing owning and operating Dry Cargo and Passenger Ships: effective: June 16, 1972, Publication (Box 572, Folder 2)
    Author: American Radio Association
  - Item 2: National agreement between American Radio Association, AFL-CIO and various Companies, Agents and Associations, Pacific Coast representing owning and operating Dry Cargo and Passenger Ships: effective: June 16, 1972, Publication (Box 572, Folder 2)
    Notes: Copy 2.
  - Item 3: National agreement between American Radio Association, AFL-CIO and various Companies, Agents and Associations, Pacific Coast representing owning and operating Tankers: effective: June 16, 1972, Publication (Box 572, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: National agreement between American Radio Association, AFL-CIO and various Companies, Agents and Associations, Pacific Coast representing owning and operating Tankers: effective: June 16, 1972, Publication (Box 572, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: National agreement between American Radio Association, AFL-CIO and Pacific Maritime Association, Pacific Coast representing owning and operating Dry Cargo and Passenger Ships: effective: June 16, 1972, Publication (Box 572, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: National agreement between American Radio Association, AFL-CIO and Pacific Maritime Association, Pacific Coast representing owning and operating Dry Cargo and Passenger Ships: effective: June 16, 1972, Publication (Box 572, Folder 2)
- Radio Officers Union, Publication (Box 572, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Newsletter - Brother Glenn Fisher recounts for ROU Membership an unusual, authentic sea story, 1981; Publication (Box 572, Folder 3)
    Author: Radio Officers Union
  - Item 2: Newsletter - Special repor from your President, Charlie Calhoun, regarding Legislative fund referendum, 1980; Publication (Box 572, Folder 3)
- Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen, Publication (Box 572, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Mediation agreement - Case No. A-10219, 1978; Publication (Box 572, Folder 4)
    Author: Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen
  - Item 2: Mediation agreement - Case No. A-10219, 1978; Publication (Box 572, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Constitution - Oct. 1, 1994, Publication (Box 572, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Constitution - Oct. 1, 1994, Publication (Box 572, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Agreement between the Southeastern Pennsylvania Transportation Authority and the Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen: Concerning an Integrated Program of Education, Assistance, and Testing for Intoxicants and Controlled Substances (including Operation Red B, 1988; Publication (Box 572, Folder 4)
    Author: Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen; Southeastern Pennsylvania Transportation Authority
- Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen, Publication (Box 572, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Constitution, 1991; Publication (Box 572, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Constitution, 1994; Publication (Box 572, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Constitution, 1994; Publication (Box 572, Folder 5)
- Railroad Workers Joint Action Committee, Publication (Box 572, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: What next for railroad labor?, 1945; Publication (Box 572, Folder 6)
    Author: Railroad Workers Joint Action Committee
- Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen, Publication (Box 572, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Supplemental Sickness Benefit plan, 1976; Publication (Box 572, Folder 7)
    Author: Provident Life and Accident Insurance Company
  - Item 2: Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen - 1901-1976, Publication (Box 572, Folder 7)
- Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen, Publication (Box 573, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Officers Report, Resolutions, and Recommendaitons of the forty-first Regular Convention, 1979; Publication (Box 573, Folder 1)
    Notes: pp. 1-127
- Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen, Publication (Box 573, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Officers Report, Resolutions, and Recommendaitons of the forty-first Regular Convention, 1979; Publication (Box 573, Folder 2)
    Notes: pp. 128-266
- Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen, Publication (Box 573, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Book no. 2 - Resolutions and Recommendations of the fortieth regular Convention -- 1976 [2 folders], Publication (Box 573, Folder 3)
    Notes: pp. 1-102(a)
- Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen, Publication (Box 573, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Book no. 2 - Resolutions and Recommendations of the fortieth regular Convention -- 1976 [2 folders], Publication (Box 573, Folder 4)
    Notes: pp. 103-193
- Railroad Yardmasters of America, Publication (Box 573, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Constitution and by-laws, 1982; Publication (Box 573, Folder 5)
    Author: Railroad Yardmasters of America
  - Item 2: Constitution and by-laws, 1982; Publication (Box 573, Folder 5)
- Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employes, Publication (Box 573, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Sometimes a party must sail against the wind, 1980; Publication (Box 573, Folder 6)
    Author: Edward Kennedy
    Notes: Transcript of speech at Georgetown University January 28, 1980
  - Item 2: Testimony of: Mr. L.E. Dennis.Appearing as a substitute witness for International President C.L. Dennis, Publication (Box 573, Folder 6)
    Author: Leslie E. Dennis
- Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employes, Publication (Box 573, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: constitution of the Grand Lodge, 1983; Publication (Box 573, Folder 7)
    Author: Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employes
  - Item 2: constitution of the Grand Lodge, 1983; Publication (Box 573, Folder 7)
- Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employes, Publication (Box 573, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Agreement between the National Railroad Passenger Corporation (Amtrak) and BRAC, 1972; Publication (Box 573, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Agreement between Universal Carloading and Distributing and BRAC, 1973; Publication (Box 573, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Mediation agreement between National Carriers' Conference Committee and BRAC, 1975; Publication (Box 573, Folder 8)
- Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employes, Publication (Box 574, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Group policy R-715, Special Accident Insurance, 1978; Publication (Box 574, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: BRAC group plan providing dental - orthodontic and vision care benefits, 1983; Publication (Box 574, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Its open season on working families, Publication (Box 574, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Operation Brotherhood, Publication (Box 574, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: I need your help to stop a cold blooded attack on the rights of working families and a direct attack on our union., 1982; Publication (Box 574, Folder 1)
    Author: R. I. Kilroy
    Notes: Correspondence
  - Item 6: BRACS drive for affirmative action in transportation clerical jobs, Publication (Box 574, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: On Nov. 8, 1983, registered voters in New York should go to the polls and cast their vote for Proposition #1 for safer transportation, Publication (Box 574, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Civil Action no. 78-1302, 1978; Publication (Box 574, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: Documents regardin Norfolk and Western Railway strike, 1978; Publication (Box 574, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: News From BRAC, 1978; Publication (Box 574, Folder 1)
    Notes: October 23, 1978.
  - Item 11: News From BRAC, 1978; Publication (Box 574, Folder 1)
    Notes: September 27, 1978.
  - Item 12: News From BRAC, 1978; Publication (Box 574, Folder 1)
    Notes: September 26, 1978.
  - Item 13: News From BRAC, 1978; Publication (Box 574, Folder 1)
    Notes: September 15, 1978.
  - Item 14: Federal Court End BRAC Ban on Striking Carriers in MAP, 1978; Publication (Box 574, Folder 1)
    Author: Bureau of National Affairs
    Notes: Current Developments no.177 (1978:Sep. 9)
  - Item 15: News From BRAC, 1978; Publication (Box 574, Folder 1)
    Notes: August 23, 1978.
  - Item 16: US Supreme Court case no.A-272, 1978; Publication (Box 574, Folder 1)
  - Item 17: To Norfolk and Western System Board Officers and Local Chairmen, 1978; Publication (Box 574, Folder 1)
    Author: Fred J. Kroll
  - Item 18: To All Members United States Congress, 1978; Publication (Box 574, Folder 1)
  - Item 19: News From BRAC, 1978; Publication (Box 574, Folder 1)
    Notes: July 20, 1978.
  - Item 20: During BRAC's recent PEP Conference in Washington, DC, approximately 800 members of our union had the opportunity to hear many political speakers, 1980; Publication (Box 574, Folder 1)
- Brotherhood Railway Carmen of the United States and Canada, Publication (Box 574, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Constitution, 1983; Publication (Box 574, Folder 2)
    Author: Brotherhood Railway Carmen of the United States and Canada
  - Item 2: Agreement covering wages and working conditions by and between Kennecott Copper Corporation, Utah Copper Division and Company's Car Inspectors: Represented by Brotherhood of Railway Carmen of United States and Canada: Effective July 1, 1974, Publication (Box 574, Folder 2)
    Author: Brotherhood Railway Carmen of the United States and Canada; Kennecott Copper Corporation
  - Item 3: Group Term Life Insurance, 1982; Publication (Box 574, Folder 2)
- Railway Labor Executives Association, Publication (Box 574, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Railway Labor Executives' Association Employee Assistance Program Workshop (excerpts from), Publication (Box 574, Folder 3)
    Author: James A. Paddock; Philip C. Fedewa
  - Item 2: The Railway Labor Executives' Association Employee Assistance Program Workshop: Instructors manual, Publication (Box 574, Folder 3)
    Author: Railway Labor Executives Association
- National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees. District 1199, Publication (Box 574, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Collective bargaining agreement between League of Voluntary Hospitals and Homes of New York and District 1199, National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees, RWDSU/AFL-CIO: 1980-1982 (Box 574, Folder 4)
    Author: Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Union. Local 1199 Retail Drug Employees Union (New York, N.Y.)
  - Item 2: Collective bargaining agreement between League of Voluntary Hospitals and Homes of New York and District 1199, National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees, RWDSU/AFL-CIO: 1980-1982, 1982-1984 (Box 574, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: 1982-1984 Municipal Coalition Economic Agreement (Box 574, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Agreement between Brooks Memorial Hospital and Buffalo and Western New York Hospital and Nursing Home Council, AFL-CIO: Begins: November 11, 1975, Ends: September 23, 1978, 1975-1978 (Box 574, Folder 4)
    Author: Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union
  - Item 5: Agreement between the Jewish Guild for the Blind and District 1199, National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees, RWDSU/AFL-CIO, 1979; Publication (Box 574, Folder 4)
    Author: National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees. District 1199
  - Item 6: Principal collective bargaining agreement between Macy's New York and Local 1-S Retail, Wholesale, Department Store Workers Union, A.F.L.-C.I.O.: agreement of March 3, 1982, Publication (Box 574, Folder 4)
    Author: Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Union. Local 1-S Department Store Workers Union (New York, N.Y.)
  - Item 7: Collective bargaining agreement between Beekman Downtown Hospital and District 1199, National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees, RWDSU/AFL-CIO: November 3, 1974 and June 30, 1976, 1974-1976 (Box 574, Folder 4)
    Author: National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees. District 1199; Beekman Downtown Hospital
  - Item 8: Collective bargaining agreement between League of Voluntary Hospitals and Homes of New York, 60 East 42nd Street, New York, N.Y., 10017, MU 7-3347 and District 1199, National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees, RWDSU/AFL-CIO, 310 West 43rd Street, 1974-1976 (Box 574, Folder 4)
    Author: League of Voluntary Hospitals and Homes of New York; National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees. District 1199
  - Item 9: Collective bargaining agreement between Macy's New York and Local 1-S Retail, Wholesale, Department Store Workers Union, A.F.L.-C.I.O.: agreement of April 1, 1978, Publication (Box 574, Folder 4)
- National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees. District 1199, Publication (Box 574, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Collective bargaining agreement between Macy's New York and Local 1-S Retail, Wholesale, Department Store Workers Union, A.F.L.-C.I.O.: agreement of March 3, 1989, Publication (Box 574, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Memorandum of understanding, the Jewish Guild for the Blind and District 1199, National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees, Publication (Box 574, Folder 5)
    Author: Jewish Guild for the Blind; National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees. District 1199
  - Item 3: Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service, Case #HC-176-3670 (2): In the matter of the arbitration between League of Voluntary Hospitals and Homes of New York and District 1199, National Union of Hospitals and Health Care Employees (AFL-CIO): Dated: Sept, 1976; Publication (Box 574, Folder 5)
    Author: Margery Gootnick
  - Item 4: American Arbitration Association League of Volunteer Hospitals and Homes of New York and District 1199, National Union of Hospitals and Health Care Employees RWDSU, AFL-CIO: Case No. 1330 0603 77: Opinion and Award of Arbitrator, 1976; Publication (Box 574, Folder 5)
    Author: Maurice C. Benewitz
- National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees. District 1199, Publication (Box 574, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Agreement between the Presbyterian Hospital in the City of New York and Local 1199.(poor photo copy), 1973; Publication (Box 574, Folder 6)
    Author: Presbyterian Hospital in the City of New York; National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees. District 1199
  - Item 2: Employment agreement of New England Health Care Employees Union, District 1199, National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees a Division of RWDSU/AFL-CIO and the State of Connecticut, Professional Health Care Unit, 1979; Publication (Box 574, Folder 6)
    Author: New England Health Care Employees Union; National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees. District 1199
  - Item 3: Agreement between Strong Memorial Hospital and National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees, RWDSU, AFL-CIO: July 1, 1976 through June 30, 1978, 1976-1978 (Box 574, Folder 6)
    Author: Strong Memorial Hospital; National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees
  - Item 4: Agreement between Strong Memorial Hospital and National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees, RWDSU, AFL-CIO: July 1, 1976 through June 30, 1978, 1976-1978 (Box 574, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Employment agreement of New England Health Care Employees Union, District 1199, National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees a Division of RWDSU/AFL-CIO and the State of Connecticut, Para-Professional Health Care Unit, 1979; Publication (Box 574, Folder 6)